

GOWRI SANKAR K

Visual Graphic Designer

Head Graphic Designer with 18 months' experience managing the complete design process, from conceptualization to delivery. Expert in interdepartmental coordination and communication. Skilled with Adobe Creative Suite (Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign, After Effects), Auto Desk (Maya, 3Ds Max, Cad), and web design applications (Dreamweaver, HTML, CSS). Able to stretch the boundaries of graphic design and digital storytelling to help my client's brands stand out

CONTACT

+91 9087327913

gowrisharan3333@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/gowri-sankarb877b4179/

https://www.behance.net/gowrisankar3333

EDUCATION

B.Voc (Multimedia & Animation)

Bharathiar University - 83%

2018 - 2021

HSC

Corporation Higher Secondary School - 67%

2017 - 2018

SSLC

S.K.A Higher Secondary School - **79%** 2015 - 2016

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe InDesign
- Adobe AfterEffects
- Adobe Premiere Pro
- Autodesk Maya
- Autodesk 3dsmax
- AutoCad

EXPERIENCE

Multimedia Trainer
MAAC| MAR - AUG 2021

- Taking Class For Students And Give a Task to Assess Them
- Learning New Things and Teach Them Clearly

O2 Designer & SMM
Zika Designs | 2021 - 2022

- Lead in the design, development, and implementation of the Design For Social Media Platform
- Creating Floor Plan For Clients Based On their Needs
- Design 3D Interior Models For Restaurants & Homes

Head Designer

O3 Brand Monk Consulting | 2021 - 2022

- Developed numerous marketing programs (logos, brochures, newsletters, infographics, presentations, and advertisements) and guaranteed that they exceeded the expectations of our clients.
- Managed up to 7 Vertical projects or tasks at a given time while under pressure to meet deadlines
- Supervise the assessment of all Designs in order to ensure the quality and accuracy of the design
- Recommended and consulted with clients on the most appropriate graphic design options based on their overall marketing goals

INTREST









